https://www.broadwaybasketeers.com/privacy

100% Satisfaction Guarantee
888-599-GIFT (4438)
Your shopping basket is empty
Looking for Ideas?
Privacy
Broadway Basketeers understands the importance of maintaining the privacy of our members and users. We are committed to using your information responsibly. We have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using our website, you expressly consent to the collection, storage, disclosure and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we make any changes to this Privacy Policy we will document those changes on this page. We encourage you to check back, from to time, and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the site will be subject to the then current privacy policy.
Information We Collect
In order to facilitate numerous products and services, to process your transactions, and to improve the quality of our services, Broadway Basketeers collects information from you at several different points on our web site. We may collect your IP address to analyze trends and customer interests as well as to administer the site, track your site movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information.
We may collect information (including name, address, telephone number, email address, IP address, user name, password, answer to security questions, information about your company or business, name and contact information about gift recipients, and, when necessary, date of birth and credit card and/or other payment/ordering information) when you place an order on our website or over the phone, return an item or make an exchange, inquire about our services or products, subscribe to receive communications from us via email or register for an account on our website, participate in one of our marketing events, are referred to us though a marketing promotion or third-party business relationship, request our catalog, are sent our products, submit information for employment consideration. This information is accessible to you by logging in to your account with your password. All of this information can be edited or deleted at any time using our website or by contacting customer service.
Using and Sharing the Information we collect?
The information collected by our site is used to process orders, to keep you informed about your order status, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you, and for statistical purposes for improving our Site. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties to charge your credit card (or process your check as appropriate), fill your order, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services for us, such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional or other support services. We will provide contact or other information necessary for the third party to provide these services for us. These parties are generally not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide our visitors with a superior customized online experience. Among other things, we use user contact information to fill orders, contact prior purchasers to inform them of their order status, to trace false orders, to remind users of events through our reminder service(s), to send our users, friends, or loved ones greetings, emails or hints to send our products through a greeting, email a friend or hint service, and to send service emails, newsletters, and promotional emails from us or third parties. We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate or segmented user behavior. This allows us to measure relative user interest in the various areas of each of our Sites for product development purposes and to improve the design of our Sites. We may also use information to notify users about updates to our sites, to complete user initiated transactions, to trace false orders and to contact users directly, or through our third-party service partners, for marketing purposes. In addition, we may seek to update you or your recipient’s personal information in our records through third party services that provide updated names, emails, addresses, phone numbers, birth dates and other information. We may then use this acquired information to enhance our services or marketing efforts to you or your recipients.
Social Media Sign in
We give our users the option to sign into Broadway Basketeers using their existing Facebook or Twitter account. The information provided to us by these sites is used to create a Broadway Basketeers account and to provide a quick and convenient method for completing an order. All collected data is compliant with the above "Information Collection" and "Using and Sharing This Information" sections.
Information collected by Cookies:
Broadway Basketeers uses cookies on the site to improve the quality of our site and services to you. A cookie is a small text file on your computer which a website sends to your computer to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies our users. Some cookies are deleted once you leave our Website (“Session cookies”) while other cookies remain after your leave our Website (“Persistent cookies”) so that you are recognized when you return to the Website. We may use persistent cookies to enable us to provide services to you, including, “Remember Me,” order history, address book, My Gift History, etc. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Information collected through Product Reviews:
You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we may ask for certain information to validate your review such as email address, photo, and your city/state/country of residence. If you submit a review, we may publish your geographic location or other anonymous information but your email address will be kept private. Additionally, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.
Security of your Personal Information?
Broadway Basketeers is committed to online data security, and for that reason we take steps to make all information received from you online as secure as reasonably possible from unauthorized access and use that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Our secure server software uses Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption technology to secure your information during transmission. In addition, your Broadway Basketeers account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a social login, you may have additional or different sign-on protection through that third party (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, etc.)
You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.
Requests from Law Enforcement:
From time to time, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
We May Change this Privacy Policy:
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to review it periodically. Our use of information, including Personal Information, is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we collect, store, or use personal information, we will document those changes on this page or contacting you directly via e-mail or other means. Your continued use of our site after any such change constitutes your agreement to any revised terms.
Questions?
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy please feel free to contact us using the information below.
Phone: 888-599-GIFT (4438)
Need Help?
888-599-GIFT (4438)
Support@bbbaskets.com
© 2020 Broadway Basketeers  |  Sitemap
All Gift Baskets Certified Kosher by OK Laboratories.
Order No.
Billing Zip Code
2020-12-11 00:47:42
